[rock guitar riff playing]
‎夏天就要结束了
Summer's almost over.
‎他们让我拥有一切
‎现在又要全部夺走
They gave me everything,
and now they're taking it all away.
‎-他们是谁？
‎-我不知道
-Who's they?
-I don't know!
‎学校
School.
‎天杀的
Son of a bitch.
‎我的暑期阅读计划还没开始
‎所以我每本读一句
I haven't even started my summer reading,
so I'm reading one line from each book.
‎“老大哥在看着你”
"Big Brother is watching you."
‎（《1984》乔治奥威尔）
‎好吧 看来是讲变态的 下一本
Okay. So it's about a perv. Next.
‎等下 新学年开始 有很多可以期待啊
Hang on, there's a lot to love
about starting a new school year.
‎新的指导教室 新课本的味道
New homerooms,
the smell of fresh textbooks,
‎早起学习
getting up early to learn.
‎切！
[Gwen, Ozzie, and Jay] Boo!
‎喂！别对她那么凶 上学挺酷的
Hey! Go easy on her.
School is cool.
‎我是说 能学东西 还有储物柜…
I mean, we learn stuff,
and there's lockers, and…
‎抱歉 宝贝 我实在高兴不起来
I'm sorry, babe. My heart's not in it.
‎“一旦你停止学习 就开始步向死亡”
"Once you stop learning, you start dying."
‎知道是谁说的吗？爱因斯坦
You know who said that? Einstein.
‎-爱因斯坦熊熊？
‎-我没话说了
-Einstein the bear?
-I'm done.
‎我完蛋了
I am so screwed.
‎这个夏天
‎我本该坚持为橄榄球做运动 结果呢
I was supposed to be working out
all summer for football. But instead,
‎我却没有
I didn't.
‎兄弟 来我的健身房
‎我会把你练得壮壮的
Bro, come to my gym. I'll get you ripped.
‎你看看
Here, check it out.
‎就像一条蛇吞了一只大老鼠
‎而且还没有消化掉
It's like a snake ate a big rat,
and it hasn't digested it yet.
‎我也想要蛇胳膊 走着
I want snake arms. Let's do this.
‎好得很
Sweet.
‎既然这是你在这里的最后一个周末
‎我换班了
Oh, since it's your last weekend,
I traded shifts at work
‎这样我们就能一起过周末了
so we can spend tomorrow together.
‎我想带你去我树林里的特别天地
I wanna take you
to my special place in the woods.
‎那是最后一次有人看到活着的她
And that was the last time
anyone saw her alive.
‎没有啦 是去野餐
No, for a picnic.
‎我想带你去眺望台 俯瞰美景
I want to show you this overlook
with an amazing view.
‎太浪漫了
That's so romantic.
‎上面有一块石头
‎长得像两个人在嘿咻
There's this rock up there,
and it looks like two people doin' it.
‎他们管它叫嘿咻石
They call it the bone stone.
‎没那么浪漫了…但我很期待
Slightly less romantic… [chuckles]
But I can't wait.
‎明天见
See you tomorrow.
‎你搞什么？要放我鸽子吗？
What the hell? You're blowing me off?
‎我们说好明天溜进乡村俱乐部的
We're supposed to sneak
into the country club tomorrow.
‎糟糕 我完全忘记了
Oh crap. I totally blanked.
‎但杰伊说得对
‎这是我们共度的最后一个周六
But Jay's right.
It's our last Saturday together.
‎妹子 这也是
‎我们共度的最后一个周六
Dude, but it's our
last Saturday together too.
‎一群有钱人想用围栏挡住我们？
A bunch of rich people put up a fence
to keep us out?
‎去他们的 他们才不比我们强
‎你说对吧 奥兹？
Screw them. They're not better than us.
Right, Ozzie?
‎那个…
I mean…
‎好吧 我不跟杰伊去了
No. I'll cancel with Jay.
‎好得很
Nice.
‎革命从明天开始
The revolution starts tomorrow.
‎我去看看我妈能不能开车送我们
I'm gonna go see if my mom can drive us.
[door closes]
‎那你要取消跟蛇胳膊的浪漫野餐？
So you're canceling
the romantic picnic with snake arms?
Um…
‎你要抛弃你最好的朋友？
-You're gonna ditch your best friend?
-Ehh…
‎你个脚踩两只船的渣渣
You're a dirty double-booker!
‎我不知道还能怎么办
‎但我觉得我能安排好 是吧？
I don't know what else to do,
but I think I can make it work, right?
‎那个…
I mean…
‎一 二 三 四
-[rock music playing]
-One, two, three, four!
‎在街上闲逛
♪ Hangin' out down the street ♪
‎和上周没什么两样
♪ The same old thing we did last week ♪
‎没什么事好做 就跟你唠唠嗑
♪ Not a thing to do ♪
♪ But talk to you ♪
‎这样挺好 这样挺好
♪ We're all all right! ♪
‎（90年代秀）
‎你好 威斯康辛！
[young woman] Hello, Wisconsin!
‎你看完财经版了没？
Are you finished with the finance section?
‎你怎么在这儿？
Why are you here?
‎我在地下室待不住了
I can't be in the basement anymore.
‎那些小孩白痴得很
Those kids are idiots.
‎我喜欢你
I like you!
‎下午三点 好的 我一定去
Okay, 3:00 p.m., great. I will be there.
[contented exclamation]
‎雷德 潘妮麦克法登来电话了
Red, that was Penny McFadden.
‎潘妮麦克法登！
Penny McFadden?!
‎是啊
[laughs] Yeah!
[both laughing]
‎我根本不知道那是谁
I have no idea who that is.
‎本地高中的人
From the high school.
‎学校的护士不知道自己怀孕了
Their school nurse didn't know
she was pregnant,
‎结果在“亮视点”生了
and just had her baby in the LensCrafters.
Eww!
‎我在那里配的隐形眼镜
That's where I get my contacts.
‎她现在在休产假
Well, she is taking
an extended maternity leave,
‎我明天去面试 争取顶替她
and I have an interview tomorrow
to replace her.
‎凯蒂 你为什么想回去工作？
Kitty, why would you
want to go back to work?
‎你知道那里有什么 对吧？
You know what's there, don't you?
‎工作
Work.
‎莉亚很快就要走了
‎我喜欢跟孩子们在一起
Leia will be leaving soon, and I really
enjoyed being around the kids.
‎没错 但你忘了 会有一个混球
Yeah, but you're forgetting about the part
where there's some jerk there
‎呼来喝去使唤你
bossing you around.
‎话说 帮我续一杯
By the way, I could use a refill.
‎别听他的 我觉得是好主意
Don't listen to him.
I think it's a great idea, Mrs. Forman.
‎我不喜欢你了
I don't like you anymore.
‎想想看
Think about it.
‎你已经多年没工作了
You haven't worked in years.
‎现在老了 迟钝了 软了
You've gotten older and slower and softer.
Uh-huh?
‎你可能需要自己再来续杯了
You might need another refill.
‎你们结婚多久了？
How long have you been married?
‎这可是菜鸟级失误
'Cause that was a rookie mistake.
[rock music playing]
‎兄弟
Bro.
‎准备好掉肉了吗？
Are you ready to shred?
‎拿我当一块马苏里拉
‎对着比萨饼使劲擦
Call me a block of mozzarella
and grate me over a pizza.
‎这就对了
That's what I'm talking about.
‎-兄弟！
-Bro!
‎-走着！
-Let's go!
‎走着！
Let's go!
["Cowboys From Hell" by Pantera playing]
[screaming]
[straining]
[Nate yelling]
[both yelling]
‎你真贴心 还帮我准备简历
You are so sweet
to help me with my résumé.
‎不像某人 一点都不支持
Some people are not so supportive.
‎我说“软了”没有恶意
Oh, I meant "softer" in a good way!
‎就像旧枕头
You know, like an old pillow.
‎我懂
I got it.
‎-好吧 跟我说说你的上一份工作
‎-我是护士长
-Okay, tell me about your last job.
-I was a head nurse.
‎太好了 你有推荐人吗？
Perfect. Do you have any references?
‎我的上司都很喜欢我
Oh, my bosses all loved me.
‎只可惜他们都死了
But they are dead.
[rock music playing]
‎快点 磨蹭鬼 别逼我扛着你走
Come on, slowpoke.
Don't make me have to carry you.
‎等一下
[panting] Wait, hang on.
‎看看阳光照在树枝上的样子
Look at the way
the sunlight is hitting those branches.
‎大自然也可以如此势不可挡
Nature can be so overwhelming.
‎很好 看过了 继续前进
Cool. Clocked it. Moving on.
‎喂
Hey.
‎急什么？我们有一整天呢
What's the rush? We've got all day.
‎这个嘛…
About that, um…
‎之前我不好意思说 我可能得早点走
I didn't want to tell you this,
but I might have to leave a little early.
‎-为什么？你还有别的事吗？
‎-没有 只是…
-Why? Do you have something else to do?
-No, no, it's just, um…
‎我想在回家前就开始转回芝加哥时间
I want to start getting back
on Chicago time before I move home.
‎-不是同一时区吗？
‎-不是…差得远呢
-Isn't it the same time there?
-No. It's… It's way different.
‎因为…湖的引力
Because of the, um…
the gravitational pull of the lake.
‎这就说得通了
That makes sense.
‎那些湖的影响力远超我们的预料呢
Those lakes are doing
more than we think they're doing.
‎是啊 我们快到了吗？
Yeah. So are we almost there?
Uh…
‎-其实我有点绕晕了
‎-我们迷路了？
-Actually, I'm kinda turned around.
-So, what, we're lost?
‎等等 我们迷路了吗？
Wait, are we lost?
‎不 我觉得应该快到了
No. No, no, no. I think we're close.
‎我来问问这个人 看他知不知道
Here, let me ask this guy if he knows.
‎不好意思
Excuse me?
‎请问你知道眺望台怎么走吗？
Do you know
where we can find the overlook?
‎知道 你们得找到蹲望台 知道吗？
Yeah, you've got to find
the under-look, okay?
‎就在那上面
And it's right above that.
‎等等 利奥？
Wait, Leo?
‎猜得真准！
Good guess! [laughs]
‎好 我来试试
Okay, let me try.
‎帕特丽夏？
Patricia?
‎没错 帕特丽夏
Yes. Patricia.
‎我就知道
I knew it.
‎-眺望台往这边走？
‎-没错 就在拐角处
Um, but the overlook is up this way?
‎-眺望台往这边走？
‎-没错 就在拐角处
Yeah, yeah. Just around the corner, man.
‎谢谢
Thanks.
‎等等！
Wait, wait, wait!
‎站在这里可以看到嘿咻石的顶端
If you stand here, you can see
the very tip of the bone stone.
‎好吧
Uh-huh.
[gasps]
[rock music playing]
[pained grunts]
[panting]
‎我浑身酸痛
I am so sore.
‎我费了20分钟才走上你家车道
It took me 20 minutes
to get up your driveway.
‎你居然以为能在一天内
‎完成整个夏天的训练量？
Why did you think you can do an entire
summer's worth of workouts in one day?
‎他从不事先考虑
He never thinks ahead.
‎现在酸得连厕所都上不了
Now he's so sore
he can't even use a toilet.
‎说得我好像很可怜似的
You're making me sound pathetic.
‎我能上厕所
I can use it.
‎就是起不来而已
I just can't get up.
‎那些饼干看起来不错
Those cookies look good.
[straining]
[pained breathing]
‎来
Here.
‎到楼下去吧 我们很忙
Now go downstairs. We're busy.
‎谢谢 宝贝
[with mouth full] Thanks, babe.
‎你知道什么能帮到你吗 亲爱的？
You know what would help you, honey?
‎在酸痛处抹点“奔肌”
Rub some Bengay on it.
‎我做大碗炒鸡蛋
‎用力过猛的时候 就用它擦肩膀
I use it on my shoulder when I go too hard
on a big bowl of scrambled eggs.
‎老天
Oh jeez.
‎也许雷德说得对
Maybe Red was right.
‎如果我做个早餐都会肩膀酸
If I get sore making breakfast,
‎面对一堆高中生 我怎么应付得来？
how can I keep up with
a bunch of high school kids?
[light instrumental music playing]
‎奶奶 我上数学课 手被纸划破了
Grandma. I got a little paper cut
in math class.
‎亲爱的 我给你拿个创可贴
Oh, honey, let me get you a Band-Aid.
‎福尔曼太太
‎我眼睛有问题 眼珠子掉出来了
Mrs. Forman, I'm having a problem
with my eye. It fell out.
‎天啊 怎么会这样？
Oh dear. How did that happen?
‎说来话长
‎你真觉得我们有时间说这些吗？
It's a long story. Do you really feel like
we have time for that?
‎纸划的伤口喷了
This paper cut's a gusher!
‎压住
Oh! Put… Put pressure on it!
‎我需要在第六节之前
‎把这个肾移植到我的身体里
I need this kidney transferred
into my body before sixth period.
‎做手术？
Surgery?!
‎她马上要生了！
‎本来要去医院的
She's having a baby now!
She was gonna go to the hospital,
‎但我说：“不用 让学校的护士处理”
but I said,
"No, let the school nurse handle it."
‎-我该怎么办？
‎-别使劲
-What do I do?
-Don't push!
‎我使劲了！
I pushed!
-[screaming]
-[baby crying]
[screaming]
‎我早跟你说过 你太不自量力了
I told you, you were in over your head.
Wah!
Wah! Wah!
[screaming]
‎这一切都有可能发生
That could all happen.
‎嗨 福尔曼太太
Hey, Mrs. Forman.
[Kitty gasps]
‎乖乖！你们俩打扮得真精神
Holy smokes! How cute are the two of you?
‎你就像刚从
‎《了不起的盖茨比》里走出来的
You look like you just
came out of The Great Gatsby.
‎我今天读了那本书里的一个句子
I read a line from that book today.
‎莉亚在哪儿？我们说好一起玩的
Where's Leia? We're supposed to hang out.
‎她和杰伊去野餐了 还没回来
Oh, she's not back yet.
She went on a picnic with Jay.
‎她和杰伊在一起？
She's with Jay?
‎-你能相信吗？
‎-能 她告诉我了
-Can you believe this?
-Yeah, she told me.
‎奥兹！
Ozzie!
‎我本来想着 她也许能成功呢
A part of me thought
she could pull it off.
‎我也同样傻傻地相信
The same foolish part of me that believed
‎麦当娜和丹尼斯罗德曼会永远在一起
that Madonna and Dennis Rodman
would be together forever.
‎随便啦 告诉莉亚 我不稀罕跟她玩
Whatever. Tell Leia she can bite me.
‎好吧 我就…自己发挥一下
Okay, I'm just…
I'm gonna put my own spin on it.
[Nate whimpers]
‎喂！看着点！
Hey! Be careful!
‎你还在啊？
Are you still here?
‎杰伊 我们为什么停下？
Jay, why are we stopping?
‎我们连现在在哪里都不知道
We have no idea where we are.
‎我知道
I know.
‎我们休息一下 享受野餐吧
Let's just take a break
and have our picnic.
‎我就可以开始准备烽火信号了
Then I can start
working on the signal fire.
‎烽火信号？咱俩现在都应该完事了
A signal fire?
I was supposed to be done with you by now.
‎跟我完事？
Done with me?
‎自从我们到了这里 你就一直怪怪的
All right, you've been acting weird
since we got here.
‎是因为我看到那只蝴蝶时哭了吗？
Is it 'cause I cried
when I saw that butterfly?
‎事实上 我…
The truth is, I…
‎我本来还约了格温
I made plans with Gwen today too.
[gasps]
‎你个脚踩两只船的渣渣！
You're a dirty double-booker!
‎我知道 我也很自责
I know. I'm not proud.
‎莉亚 你应该告诉我的
Leia, you should have just told me.
‎我知道 我不许别人碰我头发
I mean, I know I don't let anyone
touch my hair,
‎但除此之外 我还是很讲道理的
but other than that, I'm not unreasonable.
‎对不起 我不该说谎 我…
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have lied. I…
‎我不想让你失望 也不想让格温失望
I didn't want to disappoint you,
and I didn't want to disappoint Gwen.
‎-我搞砸了
‎-那芝加哥呢？
-I messed up.
-And what about Chicago?
‎跟这里同一时区
It's the same time zone.
‎伤自尊了
That one hurt.
‎-利奥？
‎-嘿 猜得真准
-Leo?
-Hey! Great guess, man.
‎嘿 我有个问题
Hey, I got a question.
‎你们知道怎么去眺望台吗？
You guys know how to get to the overlook?
‎你刚刚才给我们指了路
You just gave us
directions to the overlook.
‎太好了 我说了什么？
Oh good. What did I say?
‎真好 大家都迷路了
Great, we're all lost.
‎先跟你们说一声
Just a heads-up.
‎有只松鼠 总是跟我过不去
There's a squirrel
that's been picking on me, man.
‎它给我讲笑话 结果没抖包袱就跑了
Tells me a joke and then he runs away
before he gets to the punch line.
‎特别过分
Not cool.
‎我们要怎么回家啊？
How are we ever getting home?
‎要不你们开我的车？
Hey. Why don't you use my car?
‎它就停在通往镇子的路上
Yeah. It's parked on the road
that goes right into town.
[squirrel chittering]
‎咚咚咚个啥啊？你这混蛋！
Knock-knock what, you jerk?!
‎莉亚气死我了
I'm so pissed at Leia right now.
‎是是 她是恶魔
Yeah, yeah. She's a monster.
‎我还有要紧事要操心
I have bigger problems.
‎不好意思
Um, excuse me.
‎请把这杯柠檬汁送回去
‎我能尝到罐子的味道
I'd like to send this lemonade back.
I can taste the can.
‎我要现挤的 马上做好
I want freshly squeezed,
and I want it pronto.
‎好 能出示你的会员号码吗？
Okay. May I have your member number?
‎能出示你的失业号码吗？
May I have your unemployment number?
‎真抱歉 饮料马上就来
I'm so sorry.
I'll be right back with your drink.
‎再给这位女士拿些玉米片
And bring some nachos for the lady!
‎我来了 我知道我来晚了
‎但我可以解释
I'm here. I know I'm a little late,
but I can explain.
‎天呐 快给我说说
Oh my God, I can't wait to hear.
‎稍等 我不在乎
Oh wait. Don't care.
‎你知道我路上经历了什么吗？
‎我可是冒了生命危险的
You know what I went through to get here?
I risked my life.
‎我刚才坐的那辆车的安全带
‎居然是一条干巴的响尾蛇
I just rode in a car where the seat belt
was a dried-out rattlesnake.
‎-要不要分吃一份奶酪拼盘？
‎-我来点
-Do you want to split a cheese plate?
-I got you.
‎奶酪拼盘！
Cheese plate!
‎格温 你不是吧？真的不理我了？
Gwen, are you serious? You're ignoring me?
‎你知道今天对我多重要
‎居然还放我鸽子 跟杰伊出去玩
You knew how important this was to me,
and you still blew me off for Jay.
‎算了
Just forget it.
‎-什么算了？
‎-全都算了
-Forget what?
-Everything.
‎回你的芝加哥 别来烦我
Go back to Chicago and leave me alone.
‎什么？不好好谈谈 我是不会罢休的
What? No, I'm not leaving
until we talk about this.
‎-不好意思
‎-好主意
Excuse me?
‎-不好意思
‎-好主意
Oh, good idea. Order some food,
‎叫点吃的 咱俩正需要好好交交心
and we'll have
that heart-to-heart we need.
‎她不是这里的会员
She's not a member.
‎格温 你不至于吧
Gwen, you don't have to do this.
‎至少让我尝尝奶酪拼盘呀！
At least let me try the cheese plate!
‎这年头 他们什么人都敢放进来
They are just letting
anyone in these days.
[rock music playing]
‎谢谢你来给我打气
Thank you for coming for moral support.
‎希望不会给你带来太多不便
I hope it wasn't
too much of an inconvenience.
‎开什么玩笑？
Are you kidding?
‎赶在所有人之前先来学校
‎我现在狂飙肾上腺素
Being inside of the school before everyone
else is giving me such an adrenaline rush.
‎感觉我现在都能把汽车撂翻
I feel like I can flip over a car.
‎糟了
Oh no.
‎我的简历呢？不在啊
Where is my résumé? It's not here.
‎金枪鱼罐头？
A can of tuna?
‎嗯 我把它放在我的简历上
‎这样我就不会忘记了
Yeah, I put that on top of my résumé
so I wouldn't forget it.
‎简历很“紧要”
"To not" forget your résumé.
‎-但你还是忘了
‎-好吧 你干嘛不依不饶的？
-But you forgot it.
-Okay, why am I on trial here?
‎也许这是预兆 我就不该回去上班
Maybe this is a sign.
I have no business going back to work.
‎雷德说得对
Red was right.
‎这话我爱听
Well, I like the sound of that.
‎雷德 你来做什么？
Red, what are you doing here?
‎你忘了带简历
-You forgot your résumé.
-[Kitty sighs]
‎还有钱包
And your wallet.
‎微波炉里还有一只拖鞋
And I found a slipper in the microwave.
‎-对 我…有点紧张
‎-嗯
Yeah, yeah. I was… I was a little nervous.
‎-对 我…有点紧张
‎-嗯
Yeah.
‎来到这里 我有点胆怯
And now that I'm here,
I think I'm losing my nerve.
‎你看看 她们有多年轻
I mean, look how young they are.
‎我打赌她们都不记得
‎以前在急诊室还能抽烟
I bet none of them even remember
the days when you could smoke in the ER.
‎听我说
Look.
‎只要是你下定决心的事 你都做成了
Any time that you have set your mind
to something, you have done it.
‎我本来只想要一个孩子
‎但你还是说服我要了艾瑞克
I mean, I only wanted one kid,
and you talked me into Eric.
‎结果嘛…
And that turned out…
‎反正别放弃就对了
So don't give up.
‎你是一个好护士
You're a damn good nurse.
‎进去拿下这份工作把
Go on in there and get this job.
‎谢谢
Thank you.
‎他们根本不知道我的厉害
They are not gonna know what hit them.
‎轮到我的时候 他们会叫我的
They'll call me when it's my turn.
‎内特？你没事吧？
Nate? Are you okay?
‎我好渴
[sighs] I'm so thirsty.
‎你能帮我递一下水吗？
Can you reach that water for me?
‎把它拿到我嘴边？
And bring it to my lips?
‎帮我往我嘴里倒 好吗？剩下的我来
And tip it in my mouth? I'll do the rest.
[straining]
‎你和格温不是去乡村俱乐部了吗？
I thought you were
at the country club with Gwen.
‎我们吵架了 她因为我迟到对我发火
[sighs] We got in a fight.
She went off on me
for being a little late.
‎她说了一些很刻薄的话
She said some really mean things.
‎她是不是也说你长了狗奶头？
Did she say you had dog nipples too?
‎没有
Um… no.
‎嗯 她也没说我
[scoffs, chuckles] Yeah.
Me neither.
‎听着 不管她说什么 你都别太在意
Look. Whatever she said,
you gotta let it roll off your back.
‎有时她会这样 我是说…
She gets like this. I mean…
‎你马上要走了
You're leaving soon.
‎但我不明白
But I don't understand.
‎是我要回到芝加哥 做回隐形人
I'm the one who has to go back to Chicago
and be invisible again.
‎格温会忙着各种炫酷的事
‎在学校跟朋友打成一片
Gwen's gonna be all busy doing cool stuff,
hanging out with friends at school.
‎我知道 你眼里的格温很了不起
Look, I know Gwen is like "Gwen" to you,
‎可是…在学校就不一样了
but… it's different at school.
‎很多人并不理解她
A lot of people don't get her.
‎她会很想你的 比你想象中更严重
I think she's gonna miss you
a lot more than you realize.
‎她今天的样子可不像
She wasn't acting like it today.
‎她害我被赶出乡村俱乐部
She got me tossed out of the country club.
‎用赶出去的
Tossed.
‎就像DJ爵士杰夫
Like DJ Jazzy Jeff.
‎我也说不好
I don't know,
‎不过…可能她在用这种糟糕的方式
‎消化失去你的苦恼
but… it's probably just Gwen's
messed-up way of dealing with losing you.
‎她不会失去我的
She's not.
‎我一有时间
‎就给她打电话 写信 来看她
I'm gonna call and… and write
and visit whenever I can.
‎她是我最好的朋友
She's my best friend.
‎我无法想象没有她的生活
Can't imagine my life without her.
‎你把这些告诉她了吗？
Have you told her that?
‎可能说得太少
Maybe not enough.
‎谢谢 内特 你真聪明
Thanks, Nate. You're really smart.
‎从来没有人夸我聪明
No one's ever called me smart before.
‎听着怪怪的
It sounds weird.
‎内特
Aw, Nate.
‎好疼！
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
[rock music playing]
‎我被录用了
I got the job!
‎好样的 我就知道你能行
Attagirl! I knew you would.
‎我的知识和经验
‎给他们留下了深刻的印象
They were so impressed
with my knowledge and my experience.
‎面试我的那个女人忘了带午餐
And the woman who was interviewing me
forgot her lunch,
‎我就把我那罐金枪鱼给她了
so I gave her my can of tuna.
‎直接搞定
Sealed the deal.
[laughs]
‎只要你高兴 我就为你高兴
Well, as long as you're happy,
I am happy for you.
‎我可高兴了
I am.
‎真不敢相信 我要回去工作了
I can't believe it.
I'm going back to work.
[chuckles]
[light instrumental music playing]
‎又来了 我不是干木工的料
It happened again.
I'm not cut out for woodshop.
[suspenseful music playing]
[screaming]
‎好得很 看来以后这种事少不了了
Neat. Guess I'll be having those
all the time now.
[somber rock music playing]
‎我知道你在那里
I know you're there.
‎嘿 伙计
Hey, buddy.
‎-少来
‎-我偏要
-Don't.
-Oh, I'm gonna.
‎听着 有时候 距离可以让我们更亲近
Look. Sometimes distance
can bring you closer.
‎你有没有试过
‎让千里之外的人展现欢颜？
Have you ever made someone laugh
from thousands of miles away?
‎或者…从海滩…给朋友传真食谱？
Or… or… faxed your friend a recipe
from the beach?
‎那是美国电话电报公司的广告
That's from an AT&T commercial.
‎人家正努力呢
I'm trying here.
‎随便你 但我才不要
You can try all you want,
but I'm not doing this.
‎不 我们就要这样
Yes, we are doing this.
‎你以为我一走就再也不理你了？
You think I'm gonna leave
and never talk to you again?
‎不可能 你必须理我
That's not an option.
You have to talk to me.
‎因为有了
‎美国电话电报公司的长途套餐
Because, with AT&T's
new long-distance plan,
‎你会忍不住想理我
you can't afford not to.
‎说真的 格温 你是我最好的朋友
‎这是无论如何都不会改变的
Gwen, for real, you're my best friend,
and nothing will ever change that.
‎我会在芝加哥支持你
If I'm in Chicago, I'm here for you.
‎我会在月球上支持你
If I'm on the moon, I'm here for you.
‎等我们死了
‎我的鬼魂会缠着你的鬼魂
When we die,
my ghost will haunt your ghost.
‎你就认命吧 我赖上你了
So get used to it,
because you're stuck with me.
‎我会想你的
I'm gonna miss you.
‎我会更想你的
I'll miss you even more.
‎你在听迈克尔波顿的歌？
‎看来你真是丧到一定程度了
You're listening to Michael Bolton?
‎你在听迈克尔波顿的歌？
‎看来你真是丧到一定程度了
[chuckles] You really were
in a dark place.
‎如果你告诉任何人 我会杀了你
If you tell anyone, I'll kill you.
‎来吧 你能行
Come on. You got this.
‎用力 用力 内特！
Push. Push, Nate!
[yells]
[giggles]
‎很好
Nice.
‎你是一头猛兽
You're an animal.
‎谢谢 兄弟
Thanks, bro.
‎明天这个时候 我就能用叉子了
This time tomorrow,
I'll be able to use a fork.
[both chuckle]
‎抱歉我之前没来帮你
Hey. Sorry I wasn't here to help you out.
‎没关系 妮基也没来
That's okay. Nikki wasn't either.
‎我觉得她很生我的生气
I think she was pretty annoyed.
‎但你知道是谁帮了我吗？莉亚
But you know who did help me out? Leia.
‎你真走运 她特别好
You lucked out, man. She's pretty great.
‎她在这里时 是挺好的
Yeah, when she's here.
‎什么意思？
What do you mean?
‎哎…
Well…
‎她走了 我们要怎么继续在一起？
How am I supposed to make this work
with Leia when she leaves?
‎昨天简直一团糟
I mean, yesterday was a mess,
‎以后她远在芝加哥 事情就更复杂了
and it's only gonna get more complicated
when she's all the way in Chicago.
‎我有点害怕
I'm kinda freaked out.
‎-我想我们得认真谈谈
‎-我们就在认真谈啊
-I think we need to have a serious talk.
-We are having a serious talk.
‎我是说我和莉亚
I meant me and Leia.
Oh.
Oh!
[rock music playing]
‎字幕翻译：Zeo Niu